I remind you of the importance of understanding that by being this base around the second
それでも、2週目頃にこの基盤があることの重要性を理解する必要があることを思い出させます。
week,
週、
I have this S-shape of my epiblastic process
私のエピブラストプロセスにはS字の形があります。
which will form the notochord
それは脊索を形成します。
and finally Hensen's node, the primitive streak which
そして最終的にエンセンの結節、原始的な陥没が、
will be here, becomes a fulcrum
ここにあるものは、支点になります。
and will become a fixed point.
そして固定点になります。
And then this Hensen's node will gradually move backwards.
そして、このエンセンの結節は徐々に後方に移動します。
there is a unity
そこには一体性があります。
finally, because this will form
最終的に、これは形成されるからです。
what? It will form the base of my skull
何が？それは私の頭蓋底を形成します。
you see
ほら、
with my energy
私のエネルギーで、
the chi, the pituitary gland which will be
気、下垂体は、
there, with the
そこに、
process of the greater wings of the sphenoid
蝶形骨の大翼のプロセスと、
the petrous system
錐体システム、
and the occipital system
そして後頭システム、
and my ethmoid
そして私の篩骨、
you see, here what will happen
ほら、ここで何が起こるかというと、
well my notochord
私の脊索が、
and below what will I
そして下には何があるかというと、
I will have the development of my sacrum.
私の仙骨の発達があります。
At the level of S2,
S2のレベルで、
and then it will be the vestige of my primitive line.
そしてそれは私の原始線の痕跡となるでしょう。
So, this process here becomes a fulcrum,
したがって、このプロセスは支点になります。
that's why to free this process here,
だからこそ、このプロセスを解放するためには、
there, I must have a free sacrum,
そこには自由な仙骨が必要です。
because it is a functional unit.
なぜなら、それは機能的な単位だからです。
In this phase of development,
この発達段階では、
the embryo will have this somewhat...
胚はこのような形をしています...
racket shape with my notochord and my primitive streak, there is in this process
私の脊索と原始線を持つラケット、このプロセスには、
of growth a
成長の
field of aspiration to form the mesoderm.
中胚葉を形成するための吸引場があります。
Already, the precardiac field and all the mesoderm,
すでに、心臓前野とすべての中胚葉、
we will say intermediate, which will be pulled
つまり中間的なものは、引き伸ばされます。
by the anterior growth of
胚の前端の成長によって、
the embryo which will aspirate all the material.
すべての物質を吸引します。
in this area, you see,
この領域では、ほら、
where there will be cells in the shape
細胞が形をなしているところです。
of bottle cells which are
ボトル細胞が
aspirated towards the center, you see,
中心に向かって吸引され、分かりますか、
and which will release an acid,
そして酸を放出します、
hyaluronic acid,
ヒアルロン酸を、
which is primary at the mesenchymal level.
それは間葉レベルで一次的なものです。
It's really a level
これは本当に
important that is done by
成長のプロセスによって行われる重要な
the growth process.
レベルです。
So it's the growth that pulls
したがって、成長が情報を引き出します。この脊索軸の
the information. So the importance
重要性、
of this notochordal axis,
この中心の重要性、
the importance of this center
仙骨が自由であることの重要性。もし仙骨が自由でなければ、脊柱は
importance of having a free sacrum. If your sacrum is not free, your spine cannot
自由で
be
いられません。もし脊柱が自由でなければ、頭蓋底は
free. If your spine cannot be free, the base of your skull cannot
自由でいられません。もし頭蓋底が自由でなければ、良い屈曲
be free. If the base of your skull is not free, you cannot have good flexion
伸展ができません。つまり、神経頭蓋と
extension. That is to say, you cannot have a balance between your neurocranium
内臓頭蓋の間のバランスが取れません。これは先ほど説明したことです。
and your viscerocranium. That's what I explained earlier. It's this
これは、
It's this
眼が定着する頭蓋の上昇力です。
ascending force of the skull in which the eye will settle.
この第三の組織、
establishment of this third tissue,
中胚葉組織の形成、
mesodermal tissue,
引っ張る外胚葉の成長とともに、
with the ectodermal growth that pulls,
原始結節のほぼ退行、
the regression more or less, let's say, of the primitive node
それが下降し、分かりますか、
which descends, you see,
仙骨のレベルまで。
down to the level of the sacrum.
そして、それは非常に重要な領域になります。
And so it becomes a very important area
母親からのタンパク質情報において。
in protein information vis-à-vis the mother.
だから、ブロックされている多くの祖先のイメージは
That's why many ancestral images that are blocked
S状結腸と膀胱の間に位置しています。
are located between the sigmoid and the bladder.
そこが、母親から受け取ったイメージをブロックする場所です。
That's where you will block the images received from the mother.
そこが、それらを解放しに行くべき場所です。
That's where you have to go and clear them.
このように、これらの情報によって伝達される泌尿生殖器系の問題はすべて。
All urogenital problems, like that, transmitted by these informations.
そして、先ほど説明したように、この仙骨の下降移動力は、
And then this downward sacral migration force, as I explained earlier, at
このレベルで。